bbwpersonalsplus.com 2004-12-09

# BBW PERSONALS PLUS FOR BIG BEAUTIFUL WOMEN AND ADMIRERS - BBWPersonalsPlus.com - - 2004-12-08

Privacy Policy

This statement discloses the privacy practices for the BBWPersonalsPlus.com website. The purpose of this statement is to notify you of what personally identifiable information of yours will be collected and/or tracked by the BBWPersonalsPlus.com site, how it will be used, and what options are available to you regarding the collection, correction and/or deletion of information.

**About BBWPersonalsPlus.com and the Information We Collect**  
BBWPersonalsPlus.com is a membership-based online matchmaking service designed to provide an easy way for our members to meet each other on the Web. To accomplish this, our members create their own unique profiles and our matching technology provides them matches based on their pre-selected criteria. In order to do this, we must ask for certain personal information, which may or may not include: customer-specified BBWPersonalsPlus.com username, gender, age, ethnic background, appearance, religion, occupation, preference/lifestyle information and general geographic location. This information is used by visitors for searching and matching purposes. Much of this information is optional, and meant to be seen by members. Public information supplied by the user is intended to be viewed by visitors to the site. Public information cannot be used to identify a specific member by name, address, etc.

To process subscriptions, we may require information that includes, but is not limited to: email address, first name, last name, birth date, credit card number or checking account information for payment, a user-specified password, mailing address, zip code and telephone number. You will be notified of subscription renewal transactions when they occur. We primarily use email addresses submitted by members to verify enrollment and when forwarding anonymous e-mails from ad responders. Respondees' email addresses are not disclosed to the responder. We may also use a user's email address to send news regarding our site, but the user may choose not to receive email of this type by contacting us. Email addresses may also be used in private correspondence with the user for customer service issues. All other private information submitted by the user is confidential and will not be disclosed except as required by law or to protect members of BBWPersonalsPlus.com. All private information can be updated or deleted by the user at any time. 

**Aggregate information not directly submitted by users to BBWPersonalsPlus.com**  
This is information we collect that is not personally identifiable, such as browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all users to the site. BBWPersonalsPlus.com also logs IP addresses for systems administration purposes. IP addresses are logged to track a user's session. This gives BBWPersonalsPlus.com an idea of which parts of our site users are visiting. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a user's session will be tracked, but the user will be anonymous.

Except where you are expressly informed otherwise, we do not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your personal information except to the financial institution that processes your credit card or check transaction unless required by law or for the protection of your membership.

We have contracted with Overture services, Inc. ("Overture") to monitor certain pages of our Web site for the purpose of reporting web traffic, statistics, advertisement 'click-throughs', and/or other activities on our site. Where authorized by us, Overture may use cookies, Web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics on our Web site visitors. No personally identifiable data is collected by or transferred to Overture. For more information about how the information collected by Overture is used, please see Overture's privacy policy at http://www.overture.com/d/USm/about/company/ccprivacypolicy.jhtml. 

**Surveys and Contests**  
From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, and age). Contact and other information collected for contests will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information collected will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. 

**Public Forums**  
BBWPersonalsPlus.com makes message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose any personally identifying information. 

**Refer a Friend**  
BBWPersonalsPlus.com encourages you to refer a friend to our service. In this section you are able to send us a friend's name and email address. We simply send a one-time email to that person which contains your name and invites them to visit our site. We ask that you do not abuse this feature by entering names and addresses of those who would not be interested in BBWPersonalsPlus.com. 

**Links**  
This site contains links to other websites. Please be aware that BBWPersonalsPlus.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of other Web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Use of Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects a cookie, they will not be able to use our site. We do not and will not use cookies to collect private information from any user. 

**Security**  
BBWPersonalsPlus.com has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information stored in our database. These measures include the use of Secure Server technology during credit card transactions and administrative access to site data, as well as other proprietary security measures which are applied to all repositories and transfers of user information. 

If you have any questions about the security of our site, please contact us.

**Correcting/Updating or Removing Information**  
BBWPersonalsPlus.com provides users the following options for modifying information previously submitted. 

1\. Users may change their credit card, password and other information by going to View/Edit Profile page.   
2\. Send email via the contact form on the site.  
3\. You can send mail to the following postal address: 

BBW Personals Plus  
P.O. Box 739  
Orem, UT 84059-0739  
U.S.A.

**Email Choice/Opt-out**  
BBWPersonalsPlus.com users may use the following options if they do not wish to receive future communications.   
1\. Users may change their email options by going to View/Edit Profile and selecting Manage Emails.   
2\. Send email via the contact form on the site. 

**Legal Disclaimer**  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. 

**Changes in Our Privacy Policy**  
If we are going to use your personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify you via email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use your information in this different manner. In addition, if we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change. In some cases where we post the notice we will also email users, who have opted to receive communications from us, notifying them of the changes in our privacy practices. 

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with the BBWPersonalsPlus.com website, you can contact: 

BBW Personals Plus  
P.O. Box 739  
Orem, UT 84059-0739  
U.S.A.

Or, send email via the contact form on the site.
